Brady J. Walsh

15 Quarry Lane #6126, Malden, MA 02148

857-345-0602 | knighthawk0192@gmail.com | bradywalsh.me

SUMMARY

A self-motivated and organized professional with over 8 years' experience providing thorough and skillful technical support for a medium-scale agency. Creative problem solver with the ability to think outside the box and effectively resolve technical challenges. Uniquely able to learn new skills and quickly adapt to the ever-changing IT industry.

EDUCATION

Wentworth Institute of Technology, Boston, MA, 2014 - 2018

- B.S., cum laude, in Computer Networking; minor in Computer Science
- Network Administration, Web architecture, Databases, Security, Software Engineering

Bunker Hill Community College, Cambridge, MA, 2010 - 2013

- Associates in Computer Science
- Network Administration, Cisco systems

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Moviri, Inc., Boston, MA, 2018 – Current

Junior IT Consultant – Works directly with customers implementing technologies and processes for the performance optimization of IT systems, quality control of services provided, Capacity Planning, Business Service Automation and IT Governance & Strategy, in line with the best practices such as the guidelines provided by ITIL.

MASSACHUSETTS HEALTH CONNECTOR, Boston, MA, 2010 - 2018

IT Support Specialist – Reported to IT Process Manager, was responsible for providing desktop, network, voice and application support to Connector staff, as well as testing any new software builds and/or new technology that the Connector is working with. Prior to 2011 was an IT intern with similar responsibilities.

- Tier one desktop support for Connector staff
- Assist in the management of IT hardware and software assets, including software patch management
- Assist in testing CCA software builds
- Responsible for documenting IT policies, procedures, and protocols
- Migrated on-premise infrastructure to the cloud

SKILLS

Technology

- Development Languages: C, C++, Java, Python, Ruby, Javascript, PHP, Visual Basic, Regex, SQL, Golang
- Web Languages: HTML, CSS3, SASS, Coffee Script, Bootstrap, JQuery
- Web Frameworks: Gorilla/Mux, Ruby on Rails, NodeJS, LAMP Stack, MEAN Stack, Jekyll
- Code Version Control: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Subversion
- Databases: MySQL, SQL Server, SQLite, Oracle, MongoDB, PostgreSQL,
- Scripting Languages: Perl, Bash, Batch, Powershell, VB Script
- Office Software: MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Visio, OneNote, Project
- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux, Unix, Mac OSX
- Backup & Disaster Recovery: CloudBerry, Veeam, Barracuda, AWS S3, Acronis, Carbon
- Networking Equipment: Cisco, TP-Link, Linksys, SonicWall, pfSense
- Cloud Technologies: AWS, Google Cloud, Azure, Heroku, Firebase
- IT Governance: ITIL, COBIT
- Virtualization: VMware, VirtualBox, OpenStack, Docker, Kubernetes

INTERESTS

Security, Raspberry PI, Web Development, Traveling, Language Learning, and Cooking